golfoy.com 2015-03-16

# Privacy Policy at Golfoy.com

**We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent, and only use your information as described below. We view protection of users' privacy as a very important community principle. We understand clearly that you and your information is one of our most important assets. We store and process your information on computers located in various geographies including the United States. The servers are protected by physical as well as technological security devices offered by third party vendors. Golfoy.com does not guarantee the nature and extent of security offered by such vendors. This Privacy Policy describes the manner in which your data is collected and used by Golfoy.com. You are advised to please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By accessing the services provided by Golfoy.com you agree to the collection and use of your data by Golfoy.com in the manner provided in this Privacy Policy.** ****

## What we collect

We will automatically receive and collect certain anonymous information in standard usage logs through our Web server, including computer-identification information obtained from "cookies," sent to your browser from:

-web server cookie stored on your hard drive  
-an IP address, assigned to the computer which you use  
-the domain server through which you access our service  
-the type of computer you're using  
-the type of web browser you're using

We may collect the following personally identifiable information about you:

-name including first and last name  
-alternate email address  
-mobile phone number and contact details  
-ZIP/Postal code  
-demographic profile (like your age, gender, occupation, education, address and durables owned)  
-opinions of features on the Sites (i.e., websites that are managed, operated or licensed by the sponsors of Golfoy.com) websites  managed, operated or licensed by Golfoy.com

We may also collect the following information:

-pages on our site you visit/access  
-links you click on the Sites  
-number of times you access pages

You can terminate your account at any time. However, your information may remain stored in archive on our servers even after deletion or termination of your account.

## What we do with the information we gather

We will collect anonymous traffic information from you when you visit the Sites.

We will collect personally identifiable information about you only as part of a voluntary registration process, on-line survey, or contest, or any combination thereof.

## How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information by writing to us at contact@Golfoy.com

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at contact@Golfoy.com. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
